WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
Hey,
this is Harrison. Sorry I missed you.
Leave a message.
Hey, you didn't respond to my text,
so I thought I'd give you a call.
Maybe you're on set.
I don't know, I didn't think
you were working today, so...
But I am having a great time.
This is a really cool spot
and, you know,
I love these ladies, so all good here.
I will, uh...
I'll tell you more
when you call me back, so...
call me back.
I am at the airport.
Had my last final three hours ago.
- How was it?
- Hard...
but, you know, whatever. It's over.
You always do great,
so I wouldn't worry.
Just get on that flight
and come on and see your mama.
Okay, I'm coming, Mama.
Well, a shuttle will bring you
here from the airport,
and just come straight
to the room. I miss you.
And, Zion, please be safe, okay?
Okay, I will see you tomorrow.
Oh my God. Tomorrow.
Okay, I love you.
Love you, Mama.
- Bye.
- See you soon.
Aow!
Oh.
Uh...
Ja. Ja.
Gaitok, you are well-liked here.
You are very friendly.
But there has been more crime
on the island.
Your job is to protect the hotel.
Your job is more
than just waving to people
as they come through the gate.
Khun Lek has some ideas,
so I leave it to you two.
Good day.
Lochy!
- You want some of this?
- No. No.
I'm making you some anyway.
Saxon. Fuck, come on.
- Dad, just one sec...
- Turn it off.
I'm making a protein shake.
God.
Jesus.
Dad, I just said I'm making a shake.
Well, I'm a little jet lagged.
- It's been three days.
- Uh-huh.
Lochy, what are you doing?
- Reading.
- Why? Drink this.
- Drink it. Let's go.
- All right.
- Just chug it.
- Oh my God, dude.
Lochy, we don't do it for the taste.
We do it for the high T and BDE.
You know, girls aren't into
super jacked guys, by the way.
Really? What are they into, Piper?
Gender goblins that tuck their dicks
in between their legs like that?
Why do you have to be so gross? Stop!
Yum.
Saxon, come on, stop.
I'll give it back...
if you keep your phobias to yourself.
And don't turn our little brother
into an agender asexual like you.
Don't turn him
into a walking dildo like you.
- Give it back!
- Kids!
- Saxon.
Are one of you taking my Lorazepams?
- No, ma'am.
- No.
I just had my prescription filled,
and I could tell some are missing.
You don't have enough Lorazepam
to get through one week
at a wellness spa?
Of course, I do.
And I don't appreciate your tone, Piper.
Mom, why do you even need that stuff?
Well, you're the one who wants us
to go on this boat today with strangers.
- Fuck.
- Yeah, so what?
Certain social situations
make me anxious.
Yeah, but at home, you go to the club.
Well, that's different, you know?
I know them. They know me.
I know they're decent.
Are you okay?
Everyone at the club.
What about them?
- Dad! Please! Come on. Jeez.
- Oh my God. Your robe. Dad!
Things happen in threes.
One, the robbery. Two, the snake show.
Uh-huh.
This could be some
Final Destination shit.
Like death is coming for me.
Lightning doesn't strike
in the same place twice.
Maybe we shouldn't get on the boat.
I'm not getting on the boat.
What do you mean? Yes, you are.
I told you I'm going to Bangkok.
Yes, I remember that.
And you said your flight was at 7:00.
We'll be back by then.
Rick.
Leaving me.
- Abandoning me.
- I'm not abandoning you.
- Yes, you are.
- No, I'm not.
How long are you going for?
Couple of days.
Why? What's going on?
God. You never tell me anything.
It really hurts my feelings.
Hey, hey, hey. Don't... Don't...
Don't do that.
Knock it off.
Chelsea, come on.
Okay.
Okay, yeah, I'll...
I'll come on the boat with you.
Yay!
Yay.
It's gonna be so pretty out there.
Yeah.
Jac...
you're not supposed to have that here.
I know.
Harrison's gone a little AWOL.
I think he's on set, but, um,
I keep sending texts...
We should do something fun today.
Isn't it some kind of holiday?
- What do you wanna do?
- Well, don't we have yoga?
Oh my God. We can do yoga at home.
And we can't just sit
at the pool all week.
I mean, it's a beautiful pool,
but we should at least, one day,
sit by a different pool.
Don't you think?
- Good morning.
- Oh. Hey.
Ready to do some yoga?
We were just talking about that.
Yeah, I think we wanna have
some fun today.
So, we might skip yoga.
I love the hotel,
but it's a little dead.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Is there some place around here,
another place, a little more fun,
has more of a vibe?
You know, cocktails by the beach,
and music, and energy, and...
- I know a place you might like.
- Ooh.
It's just down the beach.
Okay. Well, you know,
Laurie's single here, so...
Yes, I... I knew this.
- Oh.
- You did?
Okay. Maybe you should meet us there.
Mm.
- I would love to, but I have...
- Okay!
Don't worry about it. She's just joking.
I'm not joking. We wanna have fun today.
All right? Let's get loose.
- Shall I arrange a driver?
- Yes.
- Right after breakfast?
- Yes!
Wonderful. Have fun
and send me pictures.
Okay, you asked for 'em!
Whoo! This is it!
Ooh, you know what?
I'm gonna go check on her.
Okay.
Hi.
- Hi.
- How are you?
You're not gonna believe it!
I was just bit by a snake.
Richard?
- Hi.
- How are you today?
I'm... I'm just gonna go grab a smoke.
I would love another session with you.
I feel there's more
to talk about. Don't you?
Yeah, I'm... going to Bangkok today.
Oh.
Uh...
May I say something?
Um... Sure, yeah.
You have touched my heart.
And I hope you will hear me
when I say...
you are not stuck.
You understand?
You can let go of your story.
You can escape the karmic cycle.
Find peace in this life.
I have hope for you.
Yeah.
It was lovely to meet you.
Likewise.
Didn't even give her a day off.
I told her she needs to get a lawyer.
Shocking.
sync and corrections by solfieri
www.MY-SUBS.com
Thank you.
I love these. Oh!
- Yoo-hoo! Hey.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- Good, and you?
- Good.
- Welcome.
Yeah, thank you.
- Gary, we have guests.
- Hi, hi, hi.
- Hello.
- Hey, how are you? I'm Saxon.
- Okay, Saxon, hi.
- Yeah.
These are the Ratcliff family.
They're staying at the hotel.
- Ratliffs. Victoria Ratliff.
- Oh, pleasure.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you. Welcome.
You work here in Thailand?
- I'm retired.
- Oh. What was your line of work?
Government work and a little investing.
Oh. Well, Timothy's in finance.
Maybe you know some of the same people.
- You never know.
- You never do.
You got anything to drink, Gary?
That's a good call.
Upstairs. We have a lounge.
- Yeah, let's go upstairs.
- Would you like to come?
Okay.
Oh, Chloe, um,
is... is there a place
I can put down my purse
- just so it's out of the way?
- Anywhere is fine.
Miss Congeniality.
It's safe there, right?
God, it's like an oligarch's boat.
He must be loaded.
- What?
- Come on.
- What is up with you now?
- Nothing.
There's nothing up with me.
Snap out of it, okay? Let's have fun.
Hey! I'm so happy you made it.
Come on!
Guys.
This is Chelsea and her man, Rick.
- Hi.
Yes, we've met.
- Hey.
- Hello.
Hello.
Chelsea's my best friend,
and I only met her two days ago.
Oh my God. So true.
- No, but it's true, right?
- Yeah!
I'm not even lying, like...
I need to use the bathroom.
Uh, yeah, downstairs in the cabin.
- Do you wanna drink something?
- Mm-hmm. Yes, please.
- What do you want?
- I'm gonna sit over here.
I don't want anything. Nothing.
- Ladies...
- Ooh!
We have arrived.
So nice.
This place is festive.
Yeah, it's fun to see something else.
- Oh.
- Mm.
Oh God.
Are you on television?
Yes.
Yes, I am. How are you?
We thought so. On holiday?
Yep. Yeah, I'm, uh...
I'm here with my girlfriends.
- Hi.
- Yep.
And you? Are you two, uh...
Are you two friends?
- Hmm.
- Oh, we've become friends.
Oh.
- I'm traveling alone.
- Okay.
And my husband died in November.
Oh, my gosh. I am so sorry.
My husband died in 2019.
Okay.
We're with a big group.
Are you with a group?
Oh, no. No, we're not. We're, um...
we're actually staying
at the White Lotus.
Oh, we wanted to see the White Lotus,
but you can't get in
unless you're a guest.
We weren't posh enough.
Okay. Cool.
Okay, have a great vacation.
Okay.
- Good day.
- Hi!
Something is off.
What?
I don't... I don't know if I like this.
Something's a little weird, am I right?
- What's weird?
I don't know. Just...
Look around.
What the actual fuck is this place?
Is this like a bargain hotel
for retirees?
- It kind of seems like that.
- Why would he send us here?
We gotta get the fuck out of here.
Where are we gon... Where...
Oh my God.
- Where are we going?
- I don't care,
but I am not staying here. No way.
- We just got drinks.
- I... Finish your drinks.
Hey! I've gotta...
Make a move!
Oh my God. Hold on!
Everything okay?
Remember that guy
I saw at dinner last night?
Mm-hmm.
It's bugging me.
I swear I know him,
but he was looking at me
like I was crazy.
I know I know him.
It's not a big deal.
Um...
Hey, I'm gonna need your help tonight.
Okay, why?
At dinner, I'm gonna tell Mom
and Dad something,
and they're gonna flip their shit.
I really need you there
for moral support.
Why are they gonna flip their shit?
'Cause I'm gonna tell them
that after I graduate,
I'm moving here.
Moving where?
I'm gonna join
that meditation center for...
yeah, like, at least a year.
I went yesterday and I looked around,
and I can just tell.
I think it's the right place for me.
No, but I th... I thought...
I thought the reason we were here
was so that you could interview
some monk for your thesis.
Okay. Okay. No, don't... don't do that.
Don't make it feel
like it's such a big deal, okay?
What about... What about me?
What about you? You'll be in college.
- Yeah, yeah, okay.
- Okay?
Okay, um, so at dinner, just,
like, say a few positive things.
I'm a marine biologist,
so I came here for the summer
- to study some corals.
- What?
I was on the beach
with a metal detector.
- Right. I gotta go, Piper.
- What? No.
- Please stay.
- I'll talk to you later.
Stop. Come back.
- See you. Come on.
- Yeah. See you, guys.
Don't do that.
Do what?
You know, sit in the corner
all day with sourpuss,
sad sack shithead.
Look over there, my nine o'clock.
But, dude, they all have like...
They all have husbands.
- No.
- Or boyfriends, or...
Dude, whatever. Who cares?
Look, all these guys
are a bunch of bald,
geriatric... pot-bellied pigs.
Okay?
Look.
These girls are thirsty
for some young fucking cum.
Dude.
Just shut up and drink this.
- Mom and Dad are right there.
- They don't care.
It's fine. Just take it.
Follow the leader. Come on. Swastika!
- Hey.
You guys want me to take your photo?
Oh, sure, thank you.
Awesome. Here, Lochy, hold that.
Yeah.
Okay, no problem.
Okay, here we go.
One, there we go...
- two, three.
- Yeah.
- Thank you so much.
- Yeah. Of course.
Uh, I'm Saxon, by the way.
And this is my little brother, Lochlan.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Hey.
- What's up?
How's it going?
- Good.
- Isn't he cute?
This guy just turned 18
in November, so, uh...
just saying, he is legal.
- Oh. That's the best part.
- Baby.
Do you want us
to take a picture with you guys?
- Uh, yeah, get in there. Come on.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, you're our co-star.
- I'll do a selfie.
Okay.
- Come on in here.
- Hey, guys.
Oh, that's good.
I love doing business in Thailand.
- Uh-huh.
- Neil, Mitch,
- all of us.
- Uh-huh.
- You go up to Laos...
- Right.
They're not just taking
ten percent off the top.
They're gonna take ten percent,
and then it's their cousin
and their cousin's cousin,
the fifth cousin, the sixth cousin.
And the next thing you know,
you have a military junta coming in,
and they're taking the whole thing
- right from underneath you. They're...
- I don't wanna cut you off.
If I ever need help hiding money
from the government
or my ex-wives, I'll call you.
All right.
Sawatdee, never.
Bye.
Thank you.
So, are you two married?
Nope, not yet, but we should be.
You should put a ring on her finger.
"It's on the table,"
is what we say.
You are all I need.
How long is this boat ride?
What's wrong with you?
You're acting strange.
- No, I'm not.
- Yes, you are.
So, what do you do, my friend?
Oh, uh...
What I do?
- I do finance.
- Finance? That's exciting.
How does finance treat you?
Good. Yeah, I got a lot of big clients.
- Uh...
- Do you?
- I am a pillar of the community.
- Are you now?
Oh yeah.
My grandfather was the governor
of North Carolina.
And my father was a...
well, a very, very,
very successful businessman.
Thank God he's dead.
Oh, both my parents.
Thank God they are...
...dead. Thank you.
Mate, we are gonna go
and catch up with you
at the bar.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Sure.
I need you to focus really hard,
- okay?
- Okay.
And just think about your number.
You thinking about it?
- Mm-hmm.
- Promise?
- Okay, 45?
- No.
Shit.
Um...
do you wanna just check in your hands
and see if there's maybe something...
- What's that?
- Stop it! Are you kidding me?
I don't... I don't know.
Where did that...
- Where did that come from?
- Oh, no. That's my number.
Come on! Get this kid a deck of cards.
He can go all night, huh?
That's crazy.
He had to know. I mean, seriously.
- I had three.
- How about we do this?
- How about we...
- They weren't very strong.
Why don't we just do some yoga...
- No, I don't wanna do yoga.
- All right.
- Then we'll give it a miss.
- I'm happy to just go to the bar, right?
Why did you send us to that place?
- You didn't like it?
- Didn't like it?
That's not what we're looking for,
Valentin.
We still have a buzz,
and the day is not over.
You need to take us,
right now, somewhere fun.
I don't think I can leave.
You're our butler,
and we need your help.
You are coming with us.
He's coming with us.
I... I can get a little crazy.
We want crazy. We wanna party.
Hold on.
Hey. Mind if I join you?
Hey.
Mm.
- Oh.
- Mm.
Hey, Dad?
Yeah?
I just want to say thank you
for bringing us here.
I know you've got a lot going on, and...
and thank you for making an effort...
giving up your phone.
It really means a lot.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
- Dad?
- I love you so much.
Mm. Well, I love you, too.
What?
Oh. Okay. Okay, thank you.
You're so perfect.
My pills are now totally missing.
Okay.
Then maybe you didn't bring them.
You're always losing things.
They were in my purse.
My whole prescription is gone.
Mom, you don't need that stuff.
Well, I feel trapped, Piper,
on a boat I don't want to be on,
with a bunch of people
I don't want to talk to.
Mom, come on. Don't be so judgmental.
Oh, you're thinking the same thing.
You're just as judgmental as I am,
if not more so, darling.
And don't you dare judge me.
I am your mother.
Sorry.
Okay, it's going to be in here.
I can tell because the look in your eye.
I know exactly what card it is.
I just need to...
Oh, yeah?
No one has a card? Is that your purse?
Just to make sure. I don't know.
- It's just... It's not anywhere here.
- Um...
It's not in your pocket.
No one took it. You didn't take it?
No.
Oh my God!
Hey, he's actually really good.
- I lost it and then it wound up here.
- Yeah.
- Okay, come on.
- What?
- Let's go.
- Come here!
- What?
Come on.
What?
What did I do now?
Are you ever going to let me in?
- Come on.
- Seriously, are you?
'Cause if not, I can't do this anymore.
I'm at the end of my rope.
It doesn't feel good...
being around this dark cloud
all the time.
And if you don't let me in,
if you don't tell me what's going on,
then I can't help you, can I?
And it's starting to feel really shitty.
What do you want to know?
Why are we here?
What's in Bangkok? Let's start there.
No, no, I don't want
to talk about that right now.
You don't ever want to talk about it.
But I want to talk about it.
I want to talk about it now.
I want to talk about it now!
What is going on?
- Okay.
- Okay, good.
Why are we here?
We're here because the fuckin' dude
who murdered my father owns this hotel.
That's why we're here.
I thought he was supposed to be here.
I read where he had a stroke,
and was in the hospital here,
but he's not here, he's in Bangkok.
So, I'm going to Bangkok.
I never knew my father.
I told you that.
He was a do-gooder.
He came to Thailand to help people.
He was trying to help these locals,
and keep a shady American
from stealing their land.
It's... I... I really don't know
all the details.
But my father was here
trying to do the right thing.
And one day, he disappeared.
And they never found him.
My mother...
told me the name of the guy who did it,
and he owns this hotel.
And half of fuckin' Thailand, I guess.
Oh my God.
Is this a bit
"You killed my father,
prepare to die," kind of?
I don't know.
Hey, watch your step.
- Whoo!
- Little stiff.
Wow!
Okay.
There's a very fun club on the beach.
It opens in an hour.
I thought maybe we can walk around town.
I'm going to call my friends to meet us.
You're going to love 'em.
So just go shopping. I'll find you.
- All right.
- Hey!
Why's everyone carrying those guns?
On Songkran, they have
water fights in the street.
It's for fun. Don't worry about it.
Thank you, Valentin.
- Okay.
- Bye.
You never listen to me.
It's kinda sweet to me.
Yeah, it's kinda...
- Ooh!
- Whoa!
Hey, you. You're very cute.
- Okay. Out of control.
- Oh God. For real.
Ooh! Hey.
Hey, please don't shoot us
with your guns, okay?
All right, we're going out
for the night.
Okay?
Okay.
Please, I'm asking you nicely, okay?
All right? I don't want to get wet.
I don't want to get wet, okay?
Thank you.
Stop! Okay? We're adults.
Where are your mothers?
Run!
Oh my God!
I'm wearing white! I'm wearing white!
Quick. Come on. Oh my God.
Get away from me!
Come on!
Oh my God!
- What... What the fuck was that?
- Oh my God.
Um, excuse me, sir.
Is there another way out of here?
No, no, no. No, no, not the front.
Is there... Is there an exit
in the back? Exit?
Khop khun kha.
- They're still out there.
- What?
- They're waiting for us.
- Huh?
- What?
- Us?
No.
Oh.
Holy shit.
"Since his wife's mysterious drowning
off the coast of Italy,
he's not responded
to investigators' request
to question him."
Huh.
Motherfucker.
Motherfucker!
Yeah, watch out for the jellyfish!
Oh, you're up here all by yourself.
Ça va?
You okay?
Um, a couple of us were talking,
and we thought it'd be fun to go
to Ko Pha Ngan tonight,
for the Full Moon Party.
What do you think?
- I can't.
- Oh.
Something I gotta deal with at home.
It's important?
It's important.
Well, could we...
could we drop you off
and then take the boat to Ko Pha Ngan?
It'd be funner with you,
but since you have something to do...
I love you.
Oh. Okay.
- Fine. Whatever. Yeah, yeah.
- Oui?
Oh! Merci. Merci, mon amour.
Okay, okay.
You're sweaty.
Thank you so much.
Just come down for a little bit.
- Don't be so antisocial.
- Okay.
- All right. Go, go, go.
- Okay?
Yeah, yeah.
Hi.
And... Whoa!
Come on in!
- Come on.
- No, no, no. Dude.
- No.
- You're next. You're next!
Cannonball!
And so, how did you and...
How did you two meet?
We met online.
My cousin met someone online,
and he actually turned out
to be a very decent person.
That's amazing.
Another?
Yeah.
Sure.
So, you live here.
You like it?
I never want to leave.
Just heard someone say that
anyone who moves to Thailand is either
looking for something or...
hiding from something.
Neither.
Just got sick of the rat race.
So, what about you?
Are you hiding or are you seeking?
I'm just on vacation with my family.
But you never know.
Hey, Mom.
They're gonna take this boat
to some island
for this big thing
called the Full Moon Party.
Lochy and I are gonna go.
You... You wanna stay
on this boat even longer?
Yeah, why not?
What? You're not coming to dinner?
I'm sorry, uh...
Well, when are you gonna be back?
Late. I mean, we'd call you guys,
but you took our phones, so...
All right, well...
You... Be safe, fellas,
and you look after your brother,
you hear?
Oh, I will.
- I love you.
- Love you, guys.
- Be safe. Come on, Piper...
- Love you.
- Let's enjoy a gorgeous meal.
- Bye, guys.
- Hey.
Chloe says they're taking the boat out
to the Full Moon Party.
It's supposed to be amazing.
Yeah, that sounds like a good time.
And I hope you have a lot of fun.
Rick, please don't go to Bangkok.
Okay?
I mean, how can you even
be sure this is the right guy?
It happened so long ago.
I mean, how do you know?
Because my mother told me
who he was on her deathbed.
You don't forget shit like that.
But what's the point?
What's the point?
The guy ruined my fucking life
from day one.
He doesn't have to answer to me?
Oh my God. You're gonna do
something fucking stupid.
I just need to look in his face,
and I need to tell him what he did to me
while he's still alive.
No, because you're not going
to just talk to him, are you?
Come on. I know you, Rick.
This is what you do.
Stay out of it.
At least let me come with you, okay?
No, you can't.
I'll be back in a couple
of days, okay? All right...
No. No, don't go.
I've got a really bad feeling.
Don't do this.
I can't miss this flight.
Oh my God, what?
- You're coming?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh my God, yes!
Hi!
All right, today has been a bust,
but we are turning it around right now.
Okay.
What happens in Thailand
stays in Thailand.
Uh-oh. What does that mean?
It means we're not dead yet, all right?
We can still be young, and hot, and fun.
- Okay. Mm-hmm.
- I mean, seriously.
- Ladies.
- Hey. How you doing? Zdraste.
- These are my friends.
- Oh.
- Aleksei and Vlad.
- Ooh!
Hi!
- Aleksei.
- Priyatno.
- Pleasure.
- And Vlad? Okay.
- Vlad.
- I'm Laurie.
- Yeah.
- Jaclyn.
- Uh, Vlad.
- Uh, hi. I'm... I'm Kate.
Pleasure. Pleasure. Yeah.
- Wow.
- Ooh.
Wow, too.
- Love your shirt.
- Ooh.
- Wow!
- I like your tattoo. It's cool.
- Oh, yeah? You like my snake?
- Wow.
I can show you,
but it goes all the way down.
- Oh, yeah?
- Ooh!
All right, guys. We've had a shitty day,
and we're not giving up.
We need you to step up.
I told them already.
They have a job to do.
We know how to make fun, you know?
Let's party.
- Yes!
- Cheers!
- Whoo!
Well, that was stressful.
Yin dee kha.
I thought I was going
to have a grand mal seizure.
What was that? That was...
That was a convention
for con men and tax cheats.
I'm sure y'all cheat on your taxes, Mom.
Well, not so badly that
we have to leave the country.
God.
You know, I wouldn't be surprised
if a few of them were actual killers.
You think men like that
only exist in bad movies?
Turns out they're real.
They're very real.
Piper, you don't know
how lucky you have it
to have a father
who's an actual boy scout.
Who isn't out chasing girls half his age
in a foreign country,
hiding from who knows what.
Yeah, I am lucky.
I gotta go ask something.
I don't know...
So... Yeah.
Well, just order me anything.
- Okay?
- Of course.
I need my phone back from you
for a few minutes.
Oh, no.
Pam, don't.
Not negotiating with you.
I want my phone, I want it now.
I'll get it from the safe.
Hmm.
Here you go.
Gosh, you're popular.
Jesus, Tim.
I've been trying to reach you
for the last 24 hours.
All right, what's going on, Chuck?
Talk to me.
Kenny Nguyen
is cooperating with the feds.
He struck some kind of deal.
We don't know all the details yet.
Motherfucker! I knew it.
He's told them everything.
I think the best we can do
is plead guilty and cut a deal.
We're just going to roll over?
Oh, you're not fuckin' serious!
I don't know
if we were ever gonna be able
to fight this,
but we're not gonna be able
to fight this now.
If I plead guilty, Chuck,
it's the end of my career.
You understand? I can't work in finance
if I plead guilty to fucking
embezzlement and fraud.
Tim, that's the least of your problems.
This is the kind of case
these guys dream of.
They're going to come after
everything you have.
Jesus fucking Christ. Well, I'll just...
You know, I tried to move
some things around last night...
We're well beyond that. I'd be shocked
if they haven't frozen
your assets already.
Frozen my assets?
What, my accounts?
Not the trust. Uh...
And they can't take my house, can they?
They can take whatever they want.
Am I going to lose my...
Am I going to lose my fucking house?
Kenny Nguyen is going to prison,
- that much I know.
- Yeah.
My hope is if we play ball,
maybe they just focus on the money,
and you just serve a few months.
Oh, just... just a few months?
In prison?
Are you fucking retarded?
Federal prison.
Most of them aren't too bad.
I know a few guys who've come out fine.
I can put you in touch with them.
I'd rather die.
You understand me?
I would rather fucking die.
What am...
What am I supposed
to tell my family, huh?
We're fucking poor now,
and I'm going to fucking prison?
This is your best advice?
Tim.
Why don't you get some better advice,
you fucking dumbass?
Fuck my fucking ass!
Would you like to give that back now?
Give... Give what back?
Your phone.
Hopefully, you won't need that again.
I won't.
Bangkok Airways Flight PG102
is now ready for boarding. Thank you.
- Hey!
- Hey, man!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Fucking clowns.
Yeah, it's... I'm...
- just a little numb.
- Oh.
What's that? Got meat in it?
Hey, full moon, baby!
Shit's about to get crazy!
Whoo!
Cheers to myself.
Cheers to you, very good.
sync and corrections by solfieri
www.MY-SUBS.com